Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Neal Lane papers
circa 1964-2011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Lane, Neal F.
MS 502
145 Linear Feet 105 boxes
Professional papers of Dr. Neal Lane from Lane's time as a professor and administrator at Rice University, as well as his time as Director of the National Science Foundation. Also included are papers from Lane's time in the White House working as the director of the Office of Science and Technology Policy.
Biographical Sketch
Neal F. Lane is Senior Fellow in Science and Technology Policy at the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy, and is the Malcolm Gillis University Professor at Rice University and professor in the Department of Physics and Astronomy. Among his many honors, Dr. Lane received the 2013 Vannevar Bush Award from the National Science Board for his service to the nation in science, technology, and public policy. Lane served in the federal government as assistant to the president for science and technology and director of the White House Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP), from August 1998 to January 2001, and as director of the National Science Foundation (NSF) and member (ex officio) of the National Science Board, from October 1993 to August 1998. Before his post with NSF, Lane was provost and professor of physics at Rice University in Houston, a position he had held since 1986. He first came to Rice in 1966, when he joined the department of physics as an assistant professor. In 1972, he became professor of physics and space physics and astronomy. He left Rice from mid-1984 to 1986 to serve as chancellor of the University of Colorado at Colorado Springs. In addition, from 1979 to 1980, while on leave from Rice, he worked at the NSF as director of the Division of Physics. Lane received his PhD, MS, and BS in physics from the University of Oklahoma.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of news clips, agendas, notes, memos, reports, Rice University course lecture notes and grade books, research notes, etc., from Lane's work at Rice University, the National Science Foundation, and the White House Office of Science and Technology Policy.
Restrictions on Access
This material is restricted due to privacy concerns, until 2037. For questions, please contact the director of the Woodson Research Center.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition information
Materials were donated by Neal Lane in 2003, 2004, and 2012.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in the following series:
Series
Series I: News clippings, reports, and press releases, 1998-2001 (Boxes 1-12)
Series II: Cabinet Files, 1998-2001 (Boxes 13-45)
Series III: OSTP, NSF, Rice, other subject files, 1964-2000 (Boxes 46-88)
Series IV: Audio/Visual, 1984-2002 (Box 89)
Series V: Baker Institute for Public Policy, work on outside boards, 2000-2011 (Boxes 90-91)
Series VI: Science & Technology (S & T) Conference, 2003 (Boxes 91-92)
Series VII: Presentations and lectures, 1993-2010 (Boxes 92-103)
Index Terms
Subjects
Education; Universities and colleges
Document Types
reports; notes; clippings (information artifacts); memorandums; agendas (administrative records); corrrespondence
Subjects (Persons)
Lane, Neal F.; Lane, Neal F.; Moore, Duncan; Smith, Jeff; Bienenstock, Arthur; Bierbaum, Rosina M.; Gwin, Holly
Subjects (Corporations)
National Science Board (U.S.); National Science Foundation (U.S.); United States. Office of Science and Technology Policy; James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy
- Series I: News clippings, reports, and press releases, 1998-2001
  - 1998 August 3-27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 August 3-12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 August 13-31 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1998 September 4-24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1998 September 25-30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 September 1-23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1998 October 1-16 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1998 October 16-30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 October 1-20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 October 21-26 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1998 November 2-11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1998 November 12-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 November 2-18 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 November 19-30 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1998 December 1-14 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1998 December 14-30 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Science Technology related, 1998 December 4-30 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, press releases, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1999 January 3-11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1999 January 12-15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1999 January 16-21 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1999 January 22-29 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 January 8-13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 January 21-31 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1999 February 1-8 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1999 February 9-20 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1999 February 22-29 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 February 1-11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 February 12-26 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1999 March 1-9 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1999 March 10-22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1999 March 23-30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1999 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 March 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 March 16-29 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1999 April 1-16 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1999 April 19-28 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1999 April 29-30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 April 2-9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 April 12-19 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 April 21-28 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1999 May 1 -10, 1999 May 1_10 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1999 May 11-19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1999 May 20-25 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1999 May 26-30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 May 3-13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 May 14-18 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 May 19-26 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 May 27-28 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Daily Press Guidance, 1999 May 27 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1999 June 1-7 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1999 June 8-16 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1999 June 17-18 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 June 3-11 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 June 14-18 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 June 21-24 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 June 28-30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, 1999 July 1-14 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1999 July 1-14 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1999 July 15-22 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1999 July 23-31 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 July 1-12 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 July 13-21 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 July 22-30 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1999 August 2-10 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 August 2-10 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 August 20-26 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 August 27-28 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1999 September 2-13 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1999 Septembet 14-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1999 September 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 September 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 September 8-15 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 September 16-22 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 September 23-28 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 September 29-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Daily Press Guidance, 1999 September 23-24 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1999 October 1-7 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1999 October 8-13 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1999 October 14-19 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1999 October 20-27 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1999 October 28-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 October 1-6 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 October 12-15 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 October 18-25 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 October 26-29 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1999 November 2-16 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1999 November 17-30 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 November 1-5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 November 8-15 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 November 17-24 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 November 29-December 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1999 December 1-9 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1999 December 10-16 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1999 December 17-22 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 December 2-7 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 December 8-15 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Science Technology related, 1999 December 16-27 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - White House News Report, 1999 December 11 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - White House News Report, 1999 December 30 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 2000 January 3-20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 2000 January 22-31 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 January 1-18 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 January 19-28 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2000 February 1-6 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2000 February 7-15 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 2000 February 16-28 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 February 1-7 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 February 8-15 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 February 16-24 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 February 25-29 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 2000 March 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 2000 March 14-31 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 March 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 March 15-21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 March 22-23 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 March 24-30 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2000 April 3-12 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2000 April 13-18 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2000 April 19-26 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2000 April 27-30 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 April 4-12 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 April 13-25 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 April 26 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 2000 May 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 2000 May 11-19 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 2000 May 21-31 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 May 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 May 11-22 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 23-31 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, statments, 2000 May 26-June 10 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2000 June 1-8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 2000 June 9-16 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 2000 June 19-27 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 June 1-13 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 June 14-22 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 June 23-30 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 2000 February - March (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2000 July 10-19 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 2000 July 20-31 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 July 5-13 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 July 14-21 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 July 24-31 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 2000 August 1-7 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 2000 August 8-17 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 August 1-14 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Science Technology related, 2000 August 15-31 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2000 September 1-14 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 2000 October 2-6 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 2000 November 2-28 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 2000 December 1-31 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - White House News Report, 2000 December 9-10 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 2001 January 3-16 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Science Technology related, 2001 February 22 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Science Technology related, 2001 April 6-17 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Science Technology related, 2001 April 24-27 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 2001 May 20-22 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Science Technology related, 2001 May 7-30 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CSSP (Center for the Study of Social Policy) handouts, clippings, 2001 May 7 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Science Technology related, 2001 June 6-18 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Series II: Cabinet Files, 1998-2001; Files relating to the Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) and the National Science Foundation. Memoranda, meeting materials, agendas, reports and notes relating to the various divisions of the OSTP: Environment, Science, Technology and National Security and International Affairs.
  - Sub-Series A: Office of Science and Technology Policy, meeting materials, 1998-2001
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 January (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 July (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 August (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 September (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Agenda, weekly meeting materials, Rosina Bierbaum with Neal Lane, 1998 September 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Agenda, weekly meeting materials, Rosina Bierbaum with Neal Lane, 1998 September 14 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 October (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 November (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1998 December (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 January (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 February (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 March (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 April (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 May (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 June (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 July (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 September (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 October (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "Designing a Report on the State of the Nation's Ecosystems," review copy, 1999 October (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 November (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 1999 December (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Environment Division, desk files, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Environment Division, memoranda, notes, reports, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Environment Division, desk files, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 February (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 March (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 April (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 May (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 June (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 July (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 August (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 September (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 October (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 November (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2000 December (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Environment Division, weekly meeting materials, 2001 January (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Lecture, Galileo High School, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Meeting materials, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Lead Rule file, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Climate change material, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Climate change material, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Climate change material, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Climate change material, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "Assessment on Climate Change," draft and talking points, 2000 June 4 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - National Assessment Blue Ribbon Panel, 2000 September 26 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - OSTP, memoranda, correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - OSTP, memoranda, correspondence, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Science Division, weekly reports, 1998 October - December (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Science Division, weekly reports, 1999 January - April (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Science Division, weekly reports, 1999 May - 2001 January (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Science Division, meeting materials, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Science Division, meeting materials, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - G-8 Okinawa Summit, 2000 May - July (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series B: Office of Science and Technology, reports, correspondence, and desk files, 1998-2001. A small number of files (Box 17, folders 21-24) include National Science Foundation correspondence
    - "Our Changing Planet," report, National Science and Technology Council (NSTC), 2000 June 29 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - StarLink corn, 2000 October (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "Effective Disaster Warnings," 2000 November (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - National Bioethics Advisory Commission report, "Ethical and Policy Issues in Research Involving Human Participants," 2000 December 19 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Holly Gwin, Chief of Staff, desk files, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Jeff Smith, Executive Assistant to the Director, desk files, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Technology Division, memoranda and correspondence, 1998 April - December (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Technology Division, memoranda and correspondence, 1999 January - December (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Technology Division, memoranda and correspondence, 2000 January - May (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Technology Division, memoranda and correspondence, 2000 June - November (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Technology Division, weekly reports, 2000 May - 2001 January (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Duncan Moore, Associate Director, Technology Division, desk files, 2000 February - August (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - National Security and International Affairs Division (NSIA), memoranda, correspondence, 1998 March - December (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - NSIA Division, memoranda, correspondence, 1999 January - July (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - NSIA Division, memoranda, correspondence, 1999 August - December (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - NSIA Division, meeting materials and weekly reports, 1999 January - March (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - NSIA Division, meeting materials and weekly reports, 1999 April - October (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - NSIA Division, weekly reports, 1999 September - December (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - NSIA Division, weekly reports, 2000 January - May (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - NSIA Division, weekly reports, May - December (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - NSIA Division, weekly progress report, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - NSIA Division, weekly progress report, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - NSIA Division, desk files, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - NSIA Division, desk files, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - NSIA Division, desk files, including Human Genome Project, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - NSIA Division, Export Controls, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - NSIA Division, desk files, 2000 January - May (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - NSIA Division, desk files, 2000 June - October (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - NSIA Division desk files, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - NSIA Division, International Agreements, 2001 January (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Defense Science Board, 2000 September 26 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Biodetection Symposium, 2000 September 8 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - National Missile Defense, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Comprehensive Test Ban Treaty, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - DOE Commission on Science and Security, speech materials, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Computer Export - Encryption Export Policy, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - ADs meeting materials, "A Legacy of Investment in Science and Technology," 1999 October 15 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - ADs meeting, 1999 October (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP), meeting materials, 1998 July -1999 March (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - OSTP, meeting materials, 1999 April - October (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - OSTP, meeting materials, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - OSTP, weekly report, 1998 August -1999 December (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Cabinet weekly reports, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Cabinet weekly reports, 1999 January - June (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Cabinet weekly reports, 1999 June - December (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Council on Environmental Quality (CEQ), weekly reports, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Intergovernmental Affairs, weekly report, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Environment Division, weekly report, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Environment Division, weekly report, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Science Division, weekly report, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Science Division, weekly report, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Technology Division, weekly report, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Technology Division, weekly report, 1998 June - December (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Technology Division, weekly report, 1999 January - April (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Technology Division, weekly report, 1999 May - December (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Technology Division, weekly reports, memoranda, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Technology Division, weekly reports, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Space and Aeronautics, agendas, related papers, 1998 March - December (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Space and Aeronautics, related papers, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Space and Aeronautics, related papers, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Draft budget, "International Energy Initiative," 1999 December 8 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - NSIA, Jones/Lane weekly meeting materials, 1998 August - December (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - OSTP, phone call logs, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - OSTP, phone call logs, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - OSTP, phone call logs, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Democratic National Committee retreat, Aspen, Colorado, 1999 July (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Meeting notes, "President's Management Council Retreat," and others, part 1, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Meeting notes, part 2, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Congressional directories, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Notes, correspondence, during new presidential administration transition, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - National Science Foundation, correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - National Science Foundation, correspondence, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - National Science Foundation, correspondence, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - National Science Foundation, correspondence, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 1999 January - June (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 1999 July (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 1999 August - September (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 1999 October (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 1999 November (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 1999 December (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 2000 January (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - OSTP, correspondence, 2000 February (Box 18, Folder 5)